# EslamEmam

# Frontend Developer

Hi, I am a frontend software development engineer. I have rich experience in web site design and building and customization. who love Programming. Developing, learning and Problem Solving. I am passionate about taking risks and solving them by Communicating & Sharing experience and knowledge.

# Contact



Eslamemam65@gmail.com

LinkedIn

Github

+201090145286

## Education

**Ahram Canadian University** 

Bachelor of Computer Science 2015 - 2019

# Skills

HTML5

CSS3

JavaScript(ES6)

React.js

**RESTfulAPIs** 

ReactRedux

**TailwindCSS** 

Git

Github

**Express** 

## **Work Experience**

#### **React Developer**

**Exios I 6th of October** 

Part-time job

#### **React Developer**

YAT I Cairo, Egypt

Internship Jan 2022 - May 2022 · 4 mos

#### **Frontend Developer**

Transit I Cairo, Egypt

Internship Aug 2021 - Dec 2021 · 6 mos

# **Professional Projects**

#### 1-Food-Resturant

Not responsive design using html and css

#### Demo

#### 2-Flip Card

Not responsive design using html and css

#### <u>Demo</u>

#### 3-Template Two

Responsive design using html and

#### <u>Demo</u>

#### 4-The-Holy-Quran react project

This project is intended for foreigners to learn and read the holy quran and listen. responsive website by using tailwind css using:Hooks,Axios Api,react router,callback function

#### <u>Demo</u>

#### 5-Quiz Application

This test consists of 10 questions, and the student can enter this test more than once, and this test is about determining the type of word whether it is a verb, noun, adverb or adjective and at the end of the test the final result and your ranking will be known. Create Client Side By React is And Server Side By Express server

Present

#### <u>GitHib</u>

#### 6-CRUD React App

Create, Read, Delete and Update Products: using json server fack api

#### GitHib